(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Today's main dish, Manila clam jjamppong)
I never thought that I'd make jjamppong in my life.
Seriously.
Can you stir-fry it?
That thing...
- In oil?
- Yes.
With this meat and Cheongyang chilli pepper.
(First, he pours julienned green onions in the wok.)
Pour all the chilli pepper here.
(A generous portion of spicy Cheongyang chilli pepper)
Is this much garlic enough?
Crushed garlic.
(Let's see.)
You should add some more.
Add a lot of it.
(Adding plenty of garlic for the extra kick)
Add the meat and stir-fry them together.
(Stir-fry it until everything is cooked)
I'll keep stirring so nothing burns on the bottom.
(Packed with flavour)
(The oil base is made by frying all these ingredients together.)
(Cranking up the heat to stir-fry)
The smoky scent is incredible.
(Thanks to his passionate assistance)
Gosh, it looks savoury.
(The flavourful oil base...)
(for the broth is ready in no time.)
Pour some more.
(Drizzle the soy sauce and stir-fry until it caramelizes.)
(It brings out the deep umami and smoky flavour.)
- All that?
- Should I put all of this in?
(Throwing in a variety of vegetables)
(Like someone generous, she piles on the vegetables.)
It smells so good.
Do you guys like julienned bamboo shoots?
Julienned bamboo shoots look delicious.
(Lastly, she brings the chilli pepper.)
(Starting to add massive amounts)
Stir-fry them together.
Stir-fry them.
(An endless shower of chilli pepper)
(When you keep stirring to make sure the chilli pepper is mixed in)
(Before you know it, an outrageously fiery masterpiece emerges.)
(She takes one quick glance.)
(Adding more chilli pepper)
That looks incredible.
(Thick)
(The more you stir-fry, the spicier it gets.)
Now I smell the jjamppong. It looks really good.
It smells so good.
- It looks spicy.
- Right.
- I can smell the spicy jjamppong.
- It looks so good.
(Stir-fry it longer so the spicy flavour gets into every bite)
(The extremely spicy jjamppong base is ready.)
(It's time to add the bottled water for the broth.)
(Pouring)
(She empties one bottle of water.)
(2 bottles)
(3 bottles)
(It keeps going in.)
(4 entire 2-litre bottles of water)
This isn't for five people anymore.
It's definitely more than ten servings.
I think it's more like 20 servings.
You're right.
It has to come to a boil.
(A large amount)
Come out for a second. Put this up here.
(The fire warrior returns.)
Let's see.
When you stack this on top...
(Stand by for a brief heat adjustment.)
The flame gets strong fast.
In the number sign shape.
(The aspiring fire warrior is learning hard.)
(Thanks to the fire warrior, the heat is at maximum.)
Gosh, thank you.
(With the flames cranked up, )
(the jjamppong broth slowly starts to boil.)
- The jjamppong started to boil.
- Okay.
Let's add the seafood and do the final taste check.
(It's time to add seafood.)
(Grabbing the small octopus and squid that Sun Young prepared)
(Dropping them in)
(Thanks to all this fresh seafood...)
(packed with the ocean flavour.)
(the spicy broth gets an extra level of refreshing flavour.)
- All right.
- I'll stir it.
And now...
Manila clams...
that we worked so hard to harvest today.
(Today's catch, Manila clams)
The star of today's show, the Manila clams are going in.
(Adding a generous amount of Manila clams)
(A glorious feast of plump Manila clams)
My gosh.
(Manila clams to add a refreshing burst of flavour to the jjamppong)
(Manila clams everywhere you look)
(Manila clams, small octopus, squid, pork, Cheongyang chilli pepper...)
(More than 13 different ingredients are added.)
It looks so delicious.
(You can't wait to taste that deep, rich broth.)
(When the broth is almost done boiling)
(Add some bok choy for the refreshing finish)
(A spicy, fiery Manila clam jjamppong broth is complete.)
(Packed with a deep rich ocean flavour)
It looks delicious.
(Looking at it is enough to make your mouth water.)
(She checks the taste for one last time.)
(How does it taste?)
- It's delicious.
- Is it good?
(It's so good that it even makes Jung Ah dance.)
All we have to do is cook the noodles.
(Once the jjamppong noodles are fully cooked)
Serve the noodles in five bowls.
(Rinse them in cold water and drain well)
If I drop this...
- And spill it?
- and spill it,
- that would be so funny.
- It'd be perfect.
Of course, that's not happening.
(I'm just kidding.)
(Thankfully, the noodles are unscathed.)
(A broth shower)
My goodness.
It looks amazing.
(A mountain of fresh Manila clams and seafood)
(Another generous pour of the spicy broth)
(An outrageously loaded bowl of jjamppong)
Manila clams are the main ingredient.
(Transferring the tangsuyuk to a nice plate)
Put it nicely.
(Drizzle it with Chef Yum's signature sauce)
My gosh.
(Moist and glossy)
It looks really good.
(Crispy on the outside and tender on the inside tangsuyuk)
(Smoky and seriously spicy pepper japchae)
(And steamed flour buns to go with it)
(Made with Manila clams we harvested ourselves)
It's really red.
(Refreshing, spicy Manila clam jjamppong)
(Smashed cucumber salad to wash away the spiciness)
(A set of 4 dishes at Siblings' Chinese Restaurant)
It's a feast at a Chinese restaurant.
We're at a Chinese restaurant today.
(A spectacular Chinese feast right before our eyes)
(I gave it everything I had.)
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
(Well done, Jung Ah.)
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you for the food.
- Bon appetit.
- Enjoy your food.
(Siblings' Chinese Restaurant is open.)
You Seok, come closer.
(Jung Seok makes sure to look after You Seok sitting at the end.)
- Can I sit closer?
- Of course.
- Can I be this close?
- Yes.
He wants to get closer to you.
(He's proud after successfully making his move.)
- Enjoy your food.
- Enjoy your food, everyone.
- Gosh.
- It looks so delicious.
It will taste even better because the Manila clams are good.
- The Manila clams are very fresh.
- Yes.
- Enjoy your food.
- I'll start with the broth.
- Me too.
Jung Ah, the food looks amazing.
I hope it's good.
(You must start having jjamppong with the broth.)
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
(Completely under its spell, he takes another bite.)
- It tastes amazing.
- It's really good.
(Sun Young takes a big spoonful of the broth.)
Gosh, it tastes so good.
(Let me try it too.)
(Yoon Seo also goes after the broth.)
(Humming)
(Jjamppong dance)
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
It's nice and spicy. It's insanely good.
(Is it that good? Jung Ah also slurps it in.)
(Humming)
- Isn't it spicy?
- Yes, it's nice and spicy.
- This is so good.
- It's really nice.
(The jjamppong broth is bursting with the spicy flavour.)
(Gulp)
(Soaked in broth, golden noodles rise to the surface.)
(A merciless bite with the chopsticks)
Try it with some Manila clams.
(Humming)
(It tastes like...)
Jung Ah, I'm a huge fan of jjamppong.
This is really good. I love jjamppong.
(Embarrassed)
Seriously.
(Taking a bite after a bold declaration of love)
Small octopus.
Do you want some?
(Yoon Seo digs in too.)
This is insane.
(It's insanely good even after another bite.)
(Onions)
This is the best jjamppong I ever had.
- What?
- Seriously.
(The younger ones' praise makes her feel proud.)
It's a lot of noodles, right?
There's so much noodle. They won't break off.
(The sheer amount is obvious at a glance.)
(But once everyone gets a taste)
(She corrects her posture.)
(While pushing her hair back, )
(she starts devouring the jjamppong.)
(Everyone locks their eyes on their jjamppong...)
(and charge.)
It's good.
(Jjamppong, you too?)
(Yes, me too)
(Stuffed cheeks)
(Bouncing feet)
(Jung Ah also digs in without caring.)
It's so spicy and good.
(Nothing but the sounds of everyone eating their jjamppong)
It's so delicious.
(While eating the noodles in a tough way)
(Extracting meat from a Manila clam)
(Humming)
(These are the Manila clams we harvested in Taean.)
Is this...
one of those Manila clams?
(How does the precious Manila clam taste?)
Have some with the Manila clams.
(Showing the furrowed brow of truth)
- It's good.
- My goodness.
(Plump)
(Pick out the clam meat and pop it right in)
The bamboo shoots are good too.
- These clams are seriously amazing.
- Yes.
They're so good.
- This is...
- The meat is very plump.
- The Manila clams are incredible.
- I agree.
- Their meat is...
- Seriously.
(They can't stop eating the big, meaty Manila clams.)
You Seok, try it.
(Fully immersed in Manila clams)
(Exclaiming)
(With endless Manila clams)
(The empty shells pile up with a satisfying clatter.)
- It tastes so good.
- Yes.
(Everyone is so deep into their jjamppong.)
Tangsuyuk got a little cold.
A moment ago...
(I forgot about the tangsuyuk.)
- The feeling of the first bite...
- It's really good.
(Without hesitation, they go for the next target.)
It's still good.
(It's tangsuyuk.)
(She takes a bite even before sitting back down.)
(Humming)
(Nodding)
(At the end of every set of chopsticks)
(A beautifully glazed piece of tangsuyuk)
(The sweet and sticky sauce stretches out.)
- Isn't it good?
- It tastes so good.
It's perfectly fried.
- Isn't it?
- Seriously.
- Right.
- The tangsuyuk is well fried.
- I agree.
- It's incredible.
It's well fried.
Ever since I made that mistake...
(Overcoming the trauma of the past)
- I never forget 170°C.
- I see.
When the oil hits 170°C,
I put in the meat.
You completely mastered how to cook tangsuyuk.
(Feeling proud)
And pepper japchae.
(All right, let's try some pepper japchae.)
Pepper japchae?
(They're busy eating so much food.)
(As Jung Ah said, he grabs a handful of pepper japchae.)
(Crunchy)
- It's a little spicy.
- Really?
I like spicy food.
(The spicy kick spreads with every chew.)
It's delicious.
It has a lot of vegetables.
(Tender meat, crisp vegetables)
It's so good.
(The siblings' pepper japchae)
- Can you give me a flower bun?
- Sure.
- I should try some.
- Here you go.
(For glossy pepper japchae, )
(fluffy flower buns are a must.)
(Pile a generous handful onto the flower bun)
It's like we're in a fairy tale.
(Wrap it up at the perfect golden ratio)
(After one juicy, fluffy bite)
(A pepper japchae wrap is born automatically.)
Pepper japchae?
Why is it so spicy?
That's why it's so good.
Smashed cucumber salad goes well with spicy food.
(A fresh smashed cucumber salad awaits.)
(With one slice of crunchy cucumber, )
(it starts again.)
- That's why it's so good.
- It's really nice.
(Jjamppong, tangsuyuk, pepper japchae)
(The siblings' infinite food loop)
- I feel so happy.
- I'm really happy.
Right now,
it's 8pm, but it's still bright outside.
- It's beautiful back there.
- The view is so pretty.
- The view is incredible.
- I know.
It's like we're shooting "Country Diaries."
- Right?
- Yes.
- This is insane.
- I feel so happy.
Look at the scenery.
It looks like a TV drama set.
The weather is beautiful too.
This is amazing.
(The sunset shimmers across the waves.)
(As the day comes to an end, the sun heads home to rest.)
(The Siblings' House beneath the legendary West Coast sunset)
This place is really beautiful.
(The food is delicious, and the scenery is beautiful.)
How did they even find a place like this?
(The siblings are busy eating and enjoying the view.)
- It's so beautiful.
- It's like we're in a fairy tale.
Jung Ah, how can you make all this food?
- I know.
I heard that you didn't cook until a few years ago.
- I learned how to cook.
- No.
If Jung Ah doesn't cook at home,
she can't cook this well.
- She must cook every day.
- Right.
Have you made jjamppong at home?
Just once.
(You made jjamppong at home?)
Seriously?
Try this.
(This was a good meal.)
(Manila clams)
(Nodding)
All that hard work paid off.
My goodness.
(We gave it everything we had.)
Today's Manila Clam Festival was great.
- It was great.
- Manila Clam Festival was amazing.
(Today's Manila Clam Festival was great.)
- Seriously, - Seriously.
starting with Cho Jung Seok's appearance...
I know.
The real thrill ended right there.
- Right.
- "Is Cho Jung Seok coming?"
- Even now...
- Underneath
(Singing as a response even though it's late)
How about a round of Balance Game?
Getting kidnapped by your current husband...
versus getting kidnapped by some random stranger.
(It's an absurd choice to make.)
Obviously, I'd choose my husband.
- A stranger would be scary.
- Right.
How about you, Jung Seok?
Me?
I'll say the same thing.
(Current wife versus a stranger)
Obviously, I'd pick Gummy. I'm her husband.
He's Gummy's husband.
- Ask me to choose...
- Yes?
- between my current husband...
- Yes.
and Matt Damon.
- She must like Matt Damon.
- Matt Damon is so handsome.
- He really is.
- Kidnapped by your husband...
- or by Matt Damon.
- Matt Damon.
I'd definitely choose Matt Damon.
(Matt Damon's name echoes across Taean.)
Getting kidnapped by your current husband...
or getting kidnapped by a wild boar?
A wild boar?
(Laughing)
- What's wrong with him?
- What?
Getting kidnapped by your current husband...
or kidnapping Matt Damon.
I prefer to kidnap Matt Damon.
(Matt Damon: I'm doomed.)
Why do you like him so much?
Are you happy just imagining it?
Balance Game is fun sometimes.
(Proud creator of the world's most hopeless Balance Game)
(Enough with this messed up Balance Game)
You're one step ahead.
This is crazy.
Should we talk about tomorrow's schedule?
- Yes.
- That sounds good.
- It's gotten very hot.
- Yes.
For tomorrow's work, you'll start early...
before the sun gets too hot.
You'll leave here tomorrow at 7:30am.
- At 7:30am?
- Leave here at 7:30am?
It's not the sea tomorrow, right?
Can you at least tell us where we're going?
Just tell us if it's on land or on land.
It has to be on land.
- "On land or on land?"
- On land.
- It can't be the sea again.
- On land...
Tell us if it's on land or at the sea.
Tell us if it's the sea or the river.
(Jung Seok wants to know if it's the sea or the river.)
You'll be working with us tomorrow, right?
- Will you work with us?
- I...
(Tomorrow as well?)
- Of course. I'm a member too.
- Once you're done working,
we'll send you home.
- Sure.
- You should work with us.
(Planning to let him leave when it's time for his other schedule)
Without coming back home.
- Will he leave after that?
- Without coming back here?
(That's so sad.)
Are you leaving?
How about being the 1st to work 3 days?
That's a bit...
He has a shoot tomorrow.
- If he didn't have a shoot...
- Go to the shoot...
and come back at night.
I'll be waiting for you.
- I'll be waiting for you.
- Really?
I'll have the blankets laid out and wait for you.
All right. In that case...
"Have the blankets laid out?"
(Why would you have the blankets laid out?)
(I can't stay here, but...)
I'll give you a personal call.
- "Be quiet."
- To let him know his plans.
(Jung Seok reached his limit.)
Is it around 9pm?
- It's 8pm.
- It's 8:20pm.
It's 8:20pm.
- Let's prepare drinks and snacks.
- Okay.
I'll clean up here.
You guys go and prepare drinks and snacks.
- We'll clean up here.
- Jung Ah, get some rest.
- Hold on.
- I'm sorry.
- Give me the leftovers.
- Isn't that better?
(He takes the leftover dishes back.)
- I'm sorry.
- Let me have some more.
- I'm not done eating.
- Stay seated.
Do you want another drink?
No, it's okay.
(One more piece...)
(and another)
Let's put on some pain patches.
(Chewing endlessly)
Yoon Seo.
(She spots him.)
Stop eating.
(Smashing his thigh)
- Why?
- No.
You'll be going on a diet as soon as you leave.
You should've made it less delicious.
It's so good that I can't stop.
I lost my control as soon as I saw the jjamppong.
This is insanely good.
The day goes by so fast.
- Let's clean up now.
- Okay.
Shall we?
(With everyone helping out, the table is cleared in no time.)
- Did you wipe it already?
- What?
- Yes, I wiped it.
- I'll take it inside.
(You Seok helps Yoon Seo who's clearing the table.)
- Give it to me.
- You can't carry both at once.
I'm a man.
(Groaning)
(A terrifying comment for the little sister)
(She runs away immediately.)
(However...)
I don't think you can carry it.
- This...
- Give it to me.
- Be careful.
- It's fine.
- Hey, I'm a man.
- Take on what you can handle.
(Laughing)
This is nothing.
Your face is very red.
(In the end, the man cleared both tables.)
How shall we do this?
The ladies should wash up first.
Then I'll go after Jung Ah.
Jung Ah, you worked hard today.
- Are you having a good time?
- Yes, it's a lot of fun.
- I like variety shows like this.
- I see.
(Under the dim lights)
(Giggling)
Did you have fun again today?
Yes, but it was hard today.
Was harvesting Manila clams hard?
It was like doing Pilates.
If harvesting wild rock seaweed was a personal training session,
- this time felt more like Pilates.
- That's an accurate comparison.
I'm done washing up.
Okay.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Who's going next?
It's me, Jong Seok.
- Jong Seok.
- He's next.
We have to hear Jong Seok sing.
- Really?
- I'd love to hear him sing...
his new song while playing the guitar.
I can't play the guitar for the new song.
- You can't?
- No.
It won't work.
- Then I will.
- Will you sing a song?
Yes, I know how to play the guitar.
- Do you know how to play it?
- You can play the guitar?
- Of course.
- That's amazing.
How so?
- I can't wait to hear it.
- I can't play the guitar.
Let's hear it.
(Everyone holds their breath to hear her performance.)
She knows how to play it.
I'd like to do it, but I don't remember it.
(This time, Yoon Seo goes up to the piano.)
Yoon Seo, play the piano.
That's good. That's it.
- Yoon Seo is...
- That's amazing.
Yoon Seo.
- Do you want to play together?
- This is all I know.
This is the only thing I can play.
(A band forms at the speed of light.)
- Start.
(The jam session begins just as quickly.)
(Whatever the siblings want to play)
(Clunk, clunk)
("Even dissonance counts as harmony" by Siblings Band)
(Pitch: 0, Rhythm: Minus 2, Fun: 100)
Jung Ah, how was our jam session?
It was excellent.
- While wearing a sheet mask...
- Goodness.
- That was fun.
- It was hilarious.
- Only with my right hand...
- I'm sorry.
- This is...
- Yes, that's it.
(He demonstrates how to play the classical guitar.)
The touch is completely different.
- It sounds lovely.
- It's different.
- He's really good at it.
- It's so sad.
- Would you play a duet with me?
- A duet?
How about playing "Spring in My Hometown?"
- Goodness.
- Please, just once.
- Sun Young, - Yes?
could you play mi on the piano?
That was sol.
(Laughing)
(That was sol.)
(After glancing back at Jung Seok who's tuning his guitar)
What kind of feeling should I play with?
Something bluesy or sweet?
Or should it feel more like a march?
Whatever feeling you want is possible.
Could you stay quiet...
- I'll keep quiet.
- until I finish tuning?
(A quiet feeling)
(It's already funny.)
Are you sensitive about tuning?
- It's tuned.
- It's done.
Let's start now.
One, two.
(Sun Young and Jung Seok's duet performance finally begins.)
(Impressed)
(Swaying side to side to the rhythm)
(After making eye contact, Jung Seok starts singing too.)
(My, he's singing too!)
(Everyone is locked in on their surprisingly solid performance.)
Jung Ah, sing it.
(Jung Ah, sing it!)
(Jung Ah adds cute little moves to her singing!)
(This performance will help them cherish their memories of Taean.)
- You know...
- Right.
- When will I get to do this again?
- Exactly.
What do you mean I'm acting weird?
- You're still being so shy.
- He just got out of the shower.
(You Seok is being so shy, and the older members find him cute.)
I find it so adorable...
- how he's been so quiet all day.
- Oh, today...
- Seriously...
- I guess he's usually chatty.
- Yes, he really is.
- But...
he loosened up by dinner time.
Usually, he won't stop talking...
- when he's around us.
- Hey, You Seok.
Were you really acting weird this morning...
because of me?
- Well, yes, it was because of you.
- It's understandable...
But seriously... What... Why was it because of me?
- It's because he was excited.
- Come on. What's wrong with you?
- I mean... It's not like that.
- It's normal to freeze up...
- when you meet someone you admire.
- Exactly.
It's like when you have a huge crush on someone,
- you get all awkward around her.
- You get all awkward.
- You just freeze up.
- That's how I felt.
You have such a great vibe, and you're so witty.
You always bring laughter to everyone around you.
I'm so jealous of all those amazing traits you have.
I think you were born with those traits.
- I agree.
- Yes, he was born with them.
Whenever I see someone like you,
- I'm amazed by your sense of humour.
- Right. He's adaptable, isn't he?
- He's very adaptable.
- Yes, he's very adaptable.
When we were chatting in the car,
I was so impressed by his witty comebacks.
- Those were so incredible.
- That's right. I mean...
He responded so quickly and wittily.
His jokes just blew my mind.
- Come on. I'm not...
- I was like, "He's amazing."
- I'm not that witty.
- "He's incredible."
- Even when he's acting...
- "That was a good one."
(They went on chatting and laughing for a while.)
- Right?
- Gosh, she's driving me crazy.
(Their first night in Taean deepened with a pleasant conversation.)
(And a brand new day has dawned.)
(Under the reddish glow of the sky, )
(a brand new morning breaks in Taean.)
(Small movements awaken the morning, )
(and everyone slowly starts the day in their own way.)
(How will the siblings' day unfold today?)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo woke up.)
Jung Ah, did you sleep well?
(They're overflowing with affection first thing in the morning.)
(Kicking her feet)
This blanket is so soft.
(Hugging her affectionately)
Go back to sleep.
- Sleep for another ten minutes.
- Okay.
(Jung Ah steps out with her work clothes.)
(Groaning)
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, I did.
- Jung Ah, good morning.
- Good morning.
Jung Ah, I'll fold the bedding.
You can go ahead and do your makeup. Please sit down.
- Jung Ah.
- That's okay.
It doesn't matter who folds the bedding.
Don't worry about it.
You see, I have something to ask you about,
Village Chief.
- Why am I the village chief?
- Then who else?
You see... By the way...
There's something I'm curious about.
(Chuckling)
- A skit first thing in the morning?
- I don't think they're up yet.
- Good morning.
- Did you sleep well, Jung Seok?
Did you sleep well, Village Chief?
- We never...
- Why am I the village chief?
- Well...
- started a skit...
I just heard her calling you "Village Chief."
(The morning skit boosts their energy.)
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, I slept well.
You set the alarm for 6:30am.
- Did I?
- Yes.
Why did I do that?
Let's slather on plenty of sunscreen.
- Slather on plenty of sunscreen.
- Plenty.
(She gets fully geared up for today's unknown task.)
It's an outfit for farm work.
I'm all set.
(All set)
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Are we leaving now?
- Are we leaving right away?
- Yes.
I'm going to draw on my eyebrows,
so please let me know when you stop the car.
She always draws on her eyebrows in the car.
(Checking her eyebrows)
- Do my eyebrows look okay?
- Oh, really?
I drew on them. How do they look?
The left one...
- I think they look okay.
- The balance is important.
- My eyebrows. Do they look okay?
- They look even.
- Do they look even?
- They look okay to me.
When we went home yesterday, my feelings were hurt.
- Why?
- My left eyebrow looked weird,
but you said it looked okay.
- Are you trying to compete with me?
- I looked...
- Oh, my goodness.
- It's not like that.
From your left side,
your left eyebrow looked fine.
- I saw it in the bathroom...
- From your left side...
and got surprised.
- You kept it from me all day long.
- Oh, so you...
Are you jealous of me?
Are you competing with me in beauty or something?
- Really?
- She clearly said...
- my eyebrows looked fine.
- I mean, I was...
I trusted her and showed my face to the cameras all day long.
- You see, - But when I went home...
there isn't a single jealous bone in my body.
- When I went home, - Why would I...
- I saw my eyebrows in the bathroom.
- Why would I be jealous...
And my left eyebrow looked weird.
Why did you tell me it looked okay?
(Lost for words)
- Because of you...
- I trusted you, Village Chief.
So I thought my eyebrows...
Why am I the village chief?
If not you, who else is the village chief?
Who's the head of this village?
- The village chief...
- It's not like I know anyone here.
- It should be you, Choon Ja.
- Who are you, then?
How many times have I told you? I'm Yum Jung Ah.
(Laughing)
Oh, Yum Jung Ah?
- You're just Yum Jung Ah?
- Yes.
(She's very happy with her eyebrows today.)
Her eyebrow episode is so funny.
They look perfect now. They're just perfect.
Did you sleep comfortably last night?
I blinked, and it was morning.
- That's great.
- Yes.
He was knocked out the moment he lay down.
- Right?
- Yes.
Did you watch me sleep?
(Chuckling)
(He watched his role model sleep.)
I wonder what we're going to do.
I'm so curious.
We're not working in Taean. We're heading to Seosan.
- Are we heading to Seosan?
- Seosan?
On our map, there are some drawings...
in Seosan too, not just in Taean.
- Seosan?
- It was either potato or garlic.
I can't remember which one.
Let's check what Seosan is famous for.
- Seosan...
- So we're doing farm work.
Guys, in Seosan,
the Mount Palbong Potato Festival is held.
- Potato?
- So it's potato?
- It's potato.
(Will they harvest potatoes today?)
(As the car rolls along busily, )
(rice paddies and fields stretch out before them.)
It's right in front of us.
Isn't that it?
(Is that our destination?)
Oh, my. This is huge.
(The endless field is already packed with people.)
There are some people who have already started working there.
(Current time: 8:30am)
(Many people are working busily early in the morning.)
(What is today's crop to harvest that's hidden beneath the soil?)
Exactly.
(Curious)
Thank you for driving.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right.
What could it be?
It's garlic.
- Right? It's garlic.
- It's garlic.
It's obvious.
Seeing how they're piled up, I guess the harvesting method is...
- pretty similar to onions.
- Right.
It's garlic, right?
(That's correct. It's garlic.)
Garlic grows well in this area.
This land was reclaimed from the sea 40 years ago,
and it has transformed into this fertile land.
(All kinds of crops thrive in this soil.)
(And the best crop among them is...)
The garlic here is raised on the sea breeze,
making it high quality.
It's rich in allicin,
which makes the garlic good for your health.
(Garlic, the comfort ingredient for Koreans)
(How do you harvest garlic?)
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you all. Hello.
I'll show you...
- how to harvest garlic.
- Okay.
You can see the garden forks over there.
This is a garlic harvesting tool.
The garlic is hidden under the soil right now.
Hold the stem with one hand like this...
and gently dig around it. Then, the garlic will pop out.
(Dig around the garlic like this, and it's done.)
(Dig in with the garden fork.)
(Next, pull it up while scooping the soil.)
(Digging in)
(Pulling it up)
You just have to loosen the soil. It's easy.
But what if I stab the garlic while digging in?
- Don't dig too close to the garlic.
- I see.
Oh, so a bit further away from the garlic?
Yes, dig a bit further away from the garlic like this.
So we should slide it in diagonally.
(That way, you won't damage the garlic.)
- Try it for now.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- You make it look so easy.
- Yes.
- Try it.
- Slide it in like this...
- It pops out, right?
- Yes, it pops out.
- Good.
- Oh, I get it.
After you finish digging up all the garlic here...
Yes.
This part is the stem.
- Cut off the stem like this.
- Yes.
Cut the stem off...
(Once you get all the garlic bulbs piled up like this...)
And put them all in the net.
- Right away?
- Put them in the net... Yes.
Got it.
Okay.
(You have to pack the net with garlic bulbs like this.)
Let's begin. We'll move forward.
- Let's begin.
- Start digging them up.
Should I put it aside after pulling it out?
- Or should I carry it?
- Just put it on the ground.
- Okay.
- And we'll cut them all at once.
(Let's dig them up first and then cut the stems off at once.)
Yes, that's good.
Good.
Nice.
(They all focus on digging up the garlic for now.)
The garlic looks so fresh and plump.
In my opinion, the key is to harvest the garlic...
without damaging it.
- Right.
- I agree.
Oh, my. This is fun.
Yes, indeed.
It's the best.
It's so cool how they grow underground like this.
(Pulling them up is satisfying.)
Look. There are two bulbs under a single stem.
- You got twins.
- Two bulbs?
(The four siblings and Jung Seok are locked in on the garlic harvest.)
This only takes a second.
How much do we get per kilogram?
One full net weighs about 10kg.
We'll pay you 15 dollars per net.
- We get 15 dollars per net?
- Did she say 10kg?
We're done for.
That means it's 1.50 dollars per kilogram.
That's so cheap.
How much money do you have left?
- Why? Why do you ask?
- We have no money left.
Why do you want to know how much we have left?
Exactly. That's just strange.
Why does it matter?
We have no money.
We have no money left.
(In that case, you should work hard, right?)
This one is big.
Oh, boy. My dear Jung Ja is...
working with us for 2 rounds, not just 1.
(How did I end up working again?)
Jung Seok, if you...
take some garlic home, will Gummy be happy?
- That's okay.
- Tell her you harvested them.
- You should take some home.
- You should.
You're really giving me some garlic?
- Sure.
- It'd be nice to cook something...
with the garlic that you harvested by yourself.
You see...
Thinking about how hard you guys should work...
to make money even after I leave...
breaks my heart. I'd feel too bad taking anything home.
That's okay. You should take some home.
Our work will be done after this.
- It'll be over.
- We'll only have fun.
- Right.
- Are you sure?
- I asked if you were sure.
- I'm not sure about it.
Village Chief, are you sure?
- Why do you keep calling me that?
- "Village Chief..."
How many times have I told you she's not the village chief?
With the way things are going, who's the village chief?
(Laughing)
Sun Young, this one is huge.
This one has a baby.
Good job, my dear Yoon Seo.
- You don't sound like you mean it.
- You did a great job.
- Say it like you mean it.
- I like everything about you.
I really like you.
- That sounds soulless.
- I mean it.
I'm nothing without my soul.
- It's "soul" in English.
- Okay.
(Nobody is whole without their soul.)
(Meanwhile, Captain Yum is full of garlic soul.)
Look at this garlic.
(Amazed)
(She dusts the dirt off carefully.)
(She quietly stacks up the garlic she harvested.)
(30 minutes have passed.)
Am I a master or what? I'm so good at this.
(I'm so good at this.)
I got the hang of it. Good.
I think I'm doing great.
- Exactly.
- What?
- We're all thinking the same thing.
- "Why am I so good at this?"
- I was thinking that too.
I can do it in one second.
I'm doing it alone, and look how fast I'm doing it.
- Ready.
- Ready, go.
(They suddenly start competing.)
- One.
- Three.
Four.
(Since we're doing this anyway, we might as well have fun with it.)
Ten.
Eleven.
(She dusts off the dirt even during the competition.)
- Thirteen, fourteen...
- Yoon Seo is doing really great.
Maybe Yoon Seo is not doing it properly.
Is it really possible to do it that fast?
- That's it. It's over.
- Okay.
- Yoon Seo dug up seventeen.
- Seventeen?
I got six.
- You're in the bottom place.
- I thought I was good at this.
- Sun Young, - Why?
you don't want to do this, do you?
(While they laugh and work, the garlic pile grows quickly.)
Oh, gosh. There's a bee here.
- A bee came to you?
- Yes.
Yoon Seo must be a flower.
(The joke really got him.)
(She lost her drive.)
You're not a boat captain...
- I'm the village chief.
- You're the village chief?
- Oh, he's the village chief.
- I'm the village chief.
- I didn't know that.
I mistook Choon Ja for the one.
Look how fast she flipped the switch.
Hearts are about to shoot out of my eyes.
(1 hour into the garlic harvest)
(They pull out the garlic.)
(And they repeat it.)
(And they dust the dirt off.)
I'm exhausted.
- We have to chop the stems too.
- Exactly.
I've been experiencing many things.
- When do we ever get to do this?
- Exactly.
- We should always be grateful.
- That motivates you.
(A thought crosses her mind.)
I don't know why,
but I feel like I've been sitting here since yesterday.
- Sitting on this stool.
- Oh, that's right.
(Am I living in yesterday or today?)
You said the same thing yesterday. You know that, right?
- "When do we ever get to do this?"
- Right.
We worked with a hoe yesterday. Today, we're digging again.
What do you call this part? It hurts so much right here.
- We dug with a hoe yesterday.
- Right.
- We're using our hands so much.
- And today,
- we're using the same muscle.
- It hurts right here, right?
What's the anatomic term for this part?
Handgrip.
- Handgrip?
- Is it called handgrip?
Isn't it handgrip?
(Let's just forget it.)
Oh, dear. I wish I could have a cup of coffee. Right?
- Yes, of course.
- You don't even have to say it.
- No need to say it.
- That's a luxury for us right now.
(If that's the case...)
How about we play a game again?
Don't you guys want...
a cup of nice, cold iced Americano?
- Jung Ah.
- Let's play a game...
- with coffee on the line.
- Do you want to play a game?
The winning team gets drinks.
Say something.
You invited me here and made me work twice.
- How about a garlic digging match?
- That's a good idea.
- One of you against one of us.
- Okay.
- If you dig up more garlic bulbs...
- In one minute.
in one minute, you win.
- Oh, that's a great idea.
- I'm confident.
What if you lose?
I haven't even considered that.
If you lose, you buy the staff coffee.
- Okay. We'll buy you coffee.
- But we don't have that much money.
I have a credit card.
- Right. She'll treat you.
- I'll treat you.
- Right. She'll buy you coffee.
- Okay.
Deal?
(Deal)
Who represents the production staff? Come forward.
- Come forward.
- Yoon Seo will represent the cast.
- Let's do this!
Bring it on.
What's your nickname?
- Nickname...
- What's your nickname?
Special Forces.
- "Special Forces?" That's not fair.
- But...
- Special Forces?
Hold on. A former Special Forces agent against me?
Isn't that a really scary place?
Actually, I have another nickname.
It's "Son of Namhae."
- Son of Namhae against...
- Namhae is also famous for garlic.
He served in the Special Forces and has farming experience.
- Son of Namhae.
- You're telling me...
Namhae? Have you ever harvested garlic?
(Of course)
- You have a lot of experience, yes?
- Yes.
He's the one who found this field.
(So what?)
(Director Son Seong Min, Special Forces, Son of Namhae)
(Garlic Field Mastermind)
- I'm getting nervous. Hold on.
- Yoon Seo, you've got this.
Yoon Seo, please do well.
Yoon Seo, bring out the youthful passion.
I'm Daughter of Jamsil.
I'll show him the power of a true Seoul native.
I'll give you the signal to start.
Get ready.
(The one who digs up more garlic bulbs in 1 minute wins.)
(If Daughter of Jamsil wins, the siblings will get coffee.)
(If Son of Namhae wins, 130 staff members will get coffee.)
(Siblings versus production staff, Garlic Digging Match for Coffee)
Get ready.
Start.
Wait.
Don't stab the garlic.
(Yoon Seo laughs.)
- Yoon Seo, stop laughing.
- Stop laughing.
I have to dig like a maniac.
(Daughter of Jamsil digs up garlic at a breakneck speed.)
- Count the garlic for me.
- Way to go!
(Son of Namhae is also fast.)
- Yoon Seo is incredible.
- You've got this.
Yoon Seo is really amazing.
That's good. Yoon Seo is doing better than him right now.
Yoon Seo, you're doing better than him.
Yoon Seo already dug up 40 bulbs.
- She's so good at this.
- Right.
(Fuelled by their encouragement...)
- Oh, that's amazing.
- You don't even need to hurry.
- You already won. You can rest.
- Exactly.
All right! Look at him. He's digging up nothing but dirt.
(He fails to dig up the garlic.)
The garlic won't come out.
- He dug three holes for no garlic.
- Son of Namhae.
(While Son of Namhae is completely flustered, )
(Daughter of Jamsil is tearing through the garlic field.)
Twenty-nine.
Thirty.
(A glaring difference in speed)
Seong Min, do your best.
(With his hands shaking, he got even more flustered.)
That's good!
He's already overwhelmed by Yoon Seo's momentum.
Impressive. Yoon Seo is amazing.
That's great. Oh, no. The garlic won't come out.
- It's over.
- Stop. It's over.
(She's sure that she won.)
- Yoon Seo is amazing.
- We don't even need to count them.
I dug them up like a crazy person.
- Eleven... Fourteen.
- Fourteen.
- And 15. He got 16.
- Fifteen.
- Thirteen.
- And 16, 17, 18...
- And 14.
- There are at least 32 here.
- She dug up so many garlic bulbs.
It's as if Yoon Seo had magic hands.
Yoon Seo is really fast.
(The siblings won a sweeping victory.)
Let's have another match sometime.
- Son of Namhae.
- What do we do?
We're bad at Omok and digging up garlic.
(That's 2 losses in a row since the Omok match in Episode 2.)
- They always lose.
- Try hard for a win next time.
I'm impressed. Yoon Seo is so good at this.
She's like the deity of garlic harvest.
Did you perhaps let us win?
- Yoon Seo is amazing.
- She's really amazing.
It's nothing.
Dig, scoop, and pull. She does it so easily and quickly.
Dig, scoop, and pull.
Yoon Seo, you can take a break.
For real.
As long as it makes you happy.
Yoon Seo is the best.
Really, she's the best.
It's my dedication to coffee.
Yoon Seo is really funny.
- Why?
- How does she do it like that?
- You...
- Yoon Seo is great at it.
How is that possible?
Push it in, and it pops out.
- Exactly. Look at her.
- That sense of...
- Right.
- She doesn't even push it in deep.
No, Yoon Seo barely pushes it in.
She must feel...
- You're right.
- this depth.
(Yoon Seo's secret is her sense of depth.)
That's what you get from an art major.
An art major.
She has a feeling for it with her hands.
That feeling is ingrained in her hands.
- An art major.
- My dexterity...
brought up my art major again.
An art major. I doubt Ewha College of Arts knew...
you were good at pulling out garlic.
Do you know how long it's been since I graduated?
(Double major: Digging up garlic)
The last time I drew... I should do some drawing.
(An art student with a garden fork instead of a brush)
Let's put some garlic in.
- True.
- Yoon Seo sure is fast.
I thought I caught up quickly,
but she's out of reach in no time.
(Daughter of Jamsil is pulling ahead alone.)
(After easily beating the production staff, )
(Yoon Seo goes at full speed.)
Dig them all up!
(Fired up)
(Garlic obsessed)
It's super plump.
(Yoon Seo keeps going even with dirt-covered knees.)
- Yoon Seo gets it in one shot.
- She's amazing at it.
One poke, and the garlic is out.
How does she do it?
- Jung Ah, - Yes?
this is how Yoon Seo holds...
- the garden fork.
- Okay.
- Was it like this?
- I hold it like this.
- Gosh, this is a technique.
- Unbelievable.
(Let's put the technique we learned to the test!)
I'll catch up to Yoon Seo's pace.
Keep it up, and we might earn quite a sum.
We'll finish in no time.
(You made me look at garlic)
(Yoon Seo's performance fired them up!)
This is a huge one.
(Coughing)
(Not even dust can stop their garlic-digging passion.)
We've dug up quite a lot.
Right? Can I move them?
(Conquered a sizeable chunk of the garlic field)
Can't we get a five-minute break?
- Yes, please.
- I'm in.
Gosh, my back.
You'll be given snacks soon,
- Five minutes?
- so take a short break.
- You want us to rest then?
- Okay.
If you gave us a five-minute break,
I was going to show it to you, you know?
- Breakdancing?
- Goodness, forget it.
Give us the break! He'll dance for us!
- No, forget it.
- Show us!
- Forget it.
- Dance! No!
- Just forget it.
- No! Sir!
Don't barge out, Ms. Sun Young Kim!
Just show us! Get us the five-minute break!
But the moves are nothing special. Here, look.
Snap. Yes.
(Still no break?)
Cho Jong Seok!
Go. Move forward while breakdancing.
She's telling him to move forward while breakdancing.
- If you... Here goes breakdancing!
- Ready...
The five-minute breakdancer is moving forward!
Here goes the breakdancer!
(Hey, you can also take a break.)
Okay, I'm only moving my arms.
A five-minute break.
(Sun Young Kim joins.)
Don't the two look like real siblings?
- They click really well.
- They really do.
(A 5-minute break! Yes!)
(Ready to dance until they get a break)
What...
Here, have some snacks!
(Applause comes naturally)
Thank you!
- Thank you!
- I brought kongguksu and makgeolli.
(Amazed)
The kongguksu looks good.
I'm having makgeolli.
- Black kongguksu.
- Kongguksu.
- Black kongguksu?
- Black kongguksu.
It's my first time seeing black kongguksu.
(Kongguksu served with black soybean broth)
- It looks delicious.
- It looks really good.
(Crunchy and refreshing whole radish kimchi)
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
(Makgeolli, a classic snack)
- You had it tough.
- Well done.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Cheers!
(Washing away the day's fatigue with a glass of makgeolli)
(Gulping down)
(You Seok drinks water as he needs to drive later.)
(Refreshed)
That's delicious.
(This is what I'm talking about.)
Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
(It's now time to taste the black kongguksu.)
(Chowing down while sitting right in the field)
Take a seat, sir.
Sit, sir.
- It's okay.
- We've got another chair.
It's okay.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- Standing up is best for oldies.
Squatting down is hard.
(Then I'll just dig into the snack.)
(Impressed)
I love it.
(The noodles taste best when soaked in the soybean broth.)
- Really?
- Yes.
(Amazed)
It's so good.
- Right?
- It's really good.
- Black kongguksu is a first for me!
- It's delicious.
Do you like kongguksu?
I do.
(Jung Ah is into the soybean broth.)
(In awe)
(The soybean broth is addicting.)
It's good. I'm serious.
Like really good.
How is it this good?
You Seok, can you hand me the soybean broth?
The what?
I need more soybean broth.
(With a refill of soybean broth)
(Gobbling down)
Black beans are good for your hair.
Hair.
(Secured a strand of hair)
It's delicious.
(About to grab a side dish)
(She couldn't resist but go back to the kongguksu.)
I get why people eat snacks after working in the countryside.
It's delicious.
(Anything is good after hard labour.)
It's good.
(They're absorbed in the snack.)
What?
It's a spider.
- Stop following me around.
- All the way here?
I'm in the middle of work.
(See you later.)
The coffee will arrive in ten minutes.
You guys can work,
- and we'll hand them out...
- Of course.
- once they get here.
Work! The bloody work!
We're snacking right now.
We'll return to work after, okay?
That lady is lying right now.
- She's lying to get you to work.
- Totally.
- It's here.
- You...
- Is the coffee here?
- Yes, but she's lying.
Oh, my gosh.
You get tricked all the time.
- But getting tricked...
- The one who's lying right now...
is you, sir.
- You get tricked all the time.
- Sir!
- Sir.
- You're not the owner, are you?
You're an actor, right?
You cast an actor, didn't you?
Sir, don't be mean to us.
All right. I'm taking these...
- if you're done eating.
- Oh, my.
Get to work.
- I'm off.
- No, wait.
But I'm still eating.
Okay, hurry.
- Gosh.
- Sir.
Now then, hurry up and dig up garlic.
- Sir. You're an actor, right?
- I'm confused right now.
He's our acting senior.
- Sir!
- Sir.
- Our acting senior.
- I'm done here.
- Don't be mean to us.
Sir.
He's good.
Let's check out how much we dug up.
In teams of two.
This requires a lot of back work.
(The final stretch of garlic digging begins)
Let's do this.
(Cut off the garlic stems.)
(Shake off the dirt and collect the bulbs in the net.)
(One person cuts the stems.)
Into the net.
(The other follows behind, gathering them up.)
The garlic sure is plump,
as farming went well this year.
- The garlic sure is big.
- For real.
- They are huge.
- Right?
(The garlic is more precious after being harvested by hand.)
I only knew garlic as something to eat.
There was no opportunity for me to harvest garlic.
(Cutting)
(And more cutting)
(Collecting them into the net)
Done. One net is full now.
We already filled one net.
- Same here.
- We're also almost done.
We're quick.
We may be quick, but look at the amount.
- True.
- There's still that much left.
(Singing work songs)
(Cutting and collecting the garlic in silence)
Have we not gotten to here yet?
We haven't. Oh, my. Unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
When will we finish?
We can do it.
Up I go.
(The sheer volume leaves everyone speechless.)
Jung Ja. I heard you were going to Seoul.
So what about going to Seoul?
(No wonder it was quiet.)
You know the saying, "You don't know what you've got until it's gone?"
Aren't I right?
Really.
- Why isn't anyone answering?
- For real.
Where's my answer? Anyone?
How long will you keep this up?
(Laughing)
If the viewers are having dinner...
without talking...
and we don't talk either, what are we to do?
We might fill about five nets.
He's off-topic.
Will we get five nets at least?
- We have enough.
- It's more than enough.
- We might get over five nets.
- Right?
There are plenty more. We might even get six.
Good. That'll get us 85 dollars. No, 90 dollars.
(6 nets times 15 dollars equals 90 dollars)
One, two... We made great progress.
(Completed 4 nets)
No, we didn't.
We earned 150 dollars yesterday.
(They need a minimum of 100 dollars to use until tomorrow.)
Why does it feel empty...
despite how much we dug up?
(They need to fill at least 7 nets.)
(Current time: 12pm, 3 hours into the garlic harvest)
The sun is rising.
- It's hot.
- It sure is hot.
It's hot.
(Groaning)
(My back hurts.)
My back.
My back hurts more today than yesterday.
The back pain is no joke.
(Being hunched over is causing back pain.)
One net is big.
A lot goes in.
(Even filling up one single net isn't easy.)
(3 more nets until their targeted number of over 7)
(Starting to act weirdly)
Jung Seok working until today...
really helps us boost the quantity.
For real, Jung Seok. Thank you.
We're running short on time.
Please focus and move fast.
(Laughing)
No more talking now.
We're running short on time.
Please focus and move fast.
(Laughing)
No more talking now.
- What...
- No more talking?
Director Se Hee. This is the first variety show...
where we're being told to focus and work only.
Is this some documentary?
I'll watch how well the show will go...
with me...
being quiet all day long.
(Rage level 1)
See? I'm a very taciturn person.
Start!
I won't say a single word from now on.
Why are you filled with rage?
(Laughing)
(I'm not talking.)
Please take a cool and slow shot of Sun Young.
Forget it!
(Turning her back on the camera)
(Moving in)
What's up with you? Seriously.
What's wrong with you?
You're practically going to bump into my face.
Really, mister.
Stop it.
Is this "Music Bank?" Stop it.
(With camera moves straight out of a music show)
Really, is this "Music Bank" or what?
Sun Young is driving me crazy.
I feel a little better now.
I just can't.
(Laughing)
- Is the first row cutting done?
- We're done cutting.
- Over there?
- Yes.
I can see the finish line too. I'm almost done.
This is fun.
No, not fun. We did a lot.
"Fun?"
(Laughing)
Is earning money fun?
It's fun.
(It's fun when you harvest a lot and earn a lot.)
One, two...
Gosh, we filled up a lot.
(The garlic nets pile up before they know it.)
I told you we did a lot.
I finished them all.
I'm done.
(When the youngest puts them in the net, )
(the third one transfers it.)
We did our best.
(Achieved their goal of 7 nets, a total of 105 dollars)
Those nets are the last, right?
The ones we each have.
(The garlic harvest is nearing its end.)
(Everyone joins forces...)
(to get every last bulb.)
Okay. How many nets in total?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Eight nets.
- Nine.
We did a lot.
Good job on harvesting and putting the garlic...
- in the nets.
- Right.
- Nine nets.
- Here's your payment...
- for the nine nets.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
(9 nets times 15 dollars)
Ninety dollars.
- No, 135 dollars.
- It's 130 dollars.
Why are you deducting money?
If it's 130 dollars, we've earned quite a lot.
(Happy)
(And)
All right. Good job.
- Thank you.
- Oh, dear.
- Oh, gosh.
- I'll carry it, Sun Young.
- I've got more for you.
- Thank you.
- Here. Garlic scapes.
- Garlic scapes!
- Yes.
- Oh, my.
- I love garlic scapes.
- Garlic scapes.
- Korean garlic scapes.
- These garlic scapes are fresh.
- Here's for Jung Seok.
- What?
This net.
- Really?
- A net for me? A net just for me?
- Yes.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
(Thank you, dear senior actor.)
(Drinking coffee right away)
(Sipping)
(Refreshing)
That hits the spot.
(Nothing short of heavenly)
(Joyfully harvested)
(Gathered with sweat and hard work, Seosan garlic)
When the garlic is laid out and dried naturally,
they won't rot.
(Shipped fresh nationwide)
Can't you stay?
Must you leave?
Must you?
I didn't think we'd say goodbye here.
- What a bummer.
- Right?
- Sun Young.
- We might cry a little...
in the car after seeing you off.
- We'll hold back right now.
- Right.
- Let's talk on the phone. Now go.
- Okay.
Okay, get in.
- No, you go first.
- No.
- You leave first.
- Gosh, I...
- The guest must leave first.
- I'm leaving.
- Go. Hurry.
- Bye.
- Bye, Yoon Seo.
- Thank you for coming.
Bye.
Bye!
(Thanks, Jung Seok!)
This feels weird.
- Seeing people off is tough.
- Yes, it's tough.
(Feeling oddly sad)
- It was fun.
- Totally.
But really...
It's different after starting out with five people.
Let's meet in a drama one day.
- You two were like actual siblings.
- Jung Seok.
- Totally.
- Yes.
Why not head home while listening to Jung Seok's music...
- to reminisce about him?
- Shall we?
- Jung Seok.
- Being in the same work...
would be fun.
Bye, Jung Seok!
Can you turn the volume up?
(You are my love)
(Calling Jung Seok)
Unbelievable. Hey, Jung Seok.
(Laughing)
- Yes, Jung Ah?
- The kids are going wild,
listening to your music.
It's like you're here with us.
(It's like you're here with us.)
I'm on the verge of doing a skit with my manager.
He's on the verge of doing a skit with his manager.
(An aftertaste as strong as the four siblings)
Get home safely, Jung Seok!
- Get home safely!
- We'll miss you!
Dear viewers.
After seeing Jung Seok off,
- we plan to...
- Sun Young is...
- wrap up today...
- talking to the camera.
Can you lower the volume, please?
To talk.
- Only if you need it.
- We'll miss him...
- Okay.
- just until we get home. Promise.
On that note, here's a song.
- "Let's Forget."
- "Promise?"
- Okay.
- "Let's Forget."
Let's forget about him now.
- I'm in!
- Let's forget about him now.
- Forget about him!
- Let's forget about him.
- Forget him. He's not special.
- Let's say goodbye to him.
Forget about him.
- In three, two, one.
- Two, one.
(Let's forget now)
(We have to forget now)
- Cho Jung Seok's...
- Cho Jung Seok?
(Cho Jung Seok's guitar)
(Cho Jung Seok's dance moves)
(Let's forget everything)
(Every skit we acted out together)
(On those drunken nights)
(Forget about them)
(Every memory of running around)
(The garlic field with Jung Seok)
(Forget about them)
(Even the music)
(We played together last night)
(All of them)
(Forget about them)
(Finding it hilarious)
(And Jung Seok's new song)
(That Jung Seok taught me)
(I'll erase it from my mind)
(Singing passionately)
- You're good at writing lyrics.
- Sun Young.
- They fit perfectly.
- For real.
- Perfectly.
- And the lyrics were improvised.
- Incredible.
- For real.
How funny. She's been talking about...
Cho Jung Seok for 30 minutes.
I made a promise to the viewers.
- It will end once we get home.
- They might get tired of it.
(Recalling the promise made to the viewers)
(30 minutes have already passed)
(We wait for Jung Seok)
(Missing Jung Seok until they arrive home)
- You Seok.
- Thank you.
- Good job, everyone.
- We came home thanks to you.
You Seok.
- I'm going to wash up.
- Okay.
(After quick showers)
I'll put on the base makeup.
Okay, Jung Ah.
- Do your base like you always do.
- Okay.
- On top of it...
- I'll put makeup on top of it.
Jung Ah, your makeup should look like you know. Right?
If you complete the base makeup,
I'll touch it up.
Dressing up sounds so much fun.
Retro style is going to be funny.
(Laughing)
(A sudden retro dress-up?)
(Before the shoot in the siblings' group chat)
(Guys, how about a family photo this time?)
(It sounds fun! Should we go with a unique concept?)
(How does a retro concept sound?)
(Okay.)
(Let's go to the local salon, do our makeup, and doll up.)
(I'll go prepared. Let's go all out!)
(I'm in!)
(I'll study some makeup looks.)
It's retro style.
Retro style?
- A local hairdresser.
- The concept is retro.
We're getting our hair done at a local salon.
For real?
- We brought our clothes.
- We brought our own clothes.
- That's...
- The makeup too.
- The clothes...
(They decide to take a retro-concept family photo.)
(First step, makeup)
- Can you colour my cheeks?
- Sure.
- I'm ready.
- You can do it.
I'll show you the art student side of me.
Show us that you're an art student.
- You're an art student.
- Yes.
Lay out everything you brought.
(Yoon Seo brought her cosmetics for today.)
(Surprised)
These are the lipsticks.
(Clattering)
(The youngest member has countless cosmetics.)
(She has a great sense of aesthetics and majored in arts.)
I think...
you could use some orange or yellow at the inner corner of your eyes.
I look good in orange.
I'll accent it a bit, and colour your lips red.
- Red lips.
- And mascara.
It'll look nice to accentuate your eyelashes with mascara.
(Jung Ah's aesthetic)
(Vivid makeup)
(Red lipstick)
(Emphasis on eyelashes)
Do you like the cool vibe or the aesthetic vibe?
I like the funny vibe.
(I actually like it funny.)
A hippie... Is there anything I can do?
Freckles.
(Sun Young's aesthetic)
(Hippie makeup, freckles, a spoonful of fun)
What should I do for You Seok?
What will you do?
- The Western American style.
- Something cool.
(You Seok's makeup will be masculine Western American style.)
Contouring makeup.
(You Seok's aesthetic)
(Western American style, contouring makeup, cowboy vibe)
I'll do the prep first.
(I'll do the prep first.)
Or I won't have time to work on their makeup.
- Yes.
- Ta-da.
(Yoon Seo's aesthetic)
(The 1990s girl group, cool style, cheerful girl style)
Shall we get started?
- Let's go.
- It's 60s, 70s, and 80s.
From 60s to 90s.
- Let's go.
Shall we travel to between 60s and 90s?
Let's go, Jung Ah.
(Siblings' beauty salon opens.)
(Various cosmetics to transform the siblings)
(And her aesthetics acknowledged by everyone)
(Today's makeup artist is Roh Yoon Sunny.)
I'll set them up first.
(First customer's aesthetic: Vivid makeup)
(The first customer is full of elegance.)
(She has a graceful and benevolent smile.)
Please look up.
(Opening wide)
- Are you covering it up?
- Yes.
Under the eyes...
What do you call the shade?
- Eye bags.
(Ms. Yum, former Miss Korea, is down-to-earth.)
They're being covered up nicely.
- Shall we go with the lines?
- I'll start on the lines.
(They hit it off.)
- Should I make it thick?
- Yes.
(Careful)
(The makeup catered to Ms. Yum is smooth-sailing.)
Freckles, blushes...
Thick eye makeup.
(Bored)
- Come here. I'll do it for you.
- No, don't.
- I'll draw your eyeline.
- It's okay.
- I'll draw your eyebrows.
- I'm fine.
You...
What am I supposed to do? I have nothing to do.
Just sing next to me.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Hippies have thick eyebrows, right?
The eyebrows are fluffy and thick.
I'll try and draw it.
(Hippie Kim couldn't wait until her turn and started first.)
- Hello.
- I'm from "Meet the People."
- Hi, I'm Kim Sun Young.
- Kim Sun Young's episode.
- Today...
Sun Young, please listen to my questions first.
- Okay.
- Sun Young, do you...
- You're so fussy.
- Sun Young.
- Yes.
- Can you come and sit on my left?
- Why?
- Is it my turn?
- She'll do me.
- I'll alternate between you two.
- When will you do me?
- You're last.
You're a famous makeup artist in Seoul.
I need to work on famous celebrities first.
- So...
- Is that why I'm last?
How did you become...
so good at makeup?
- Please explain.
- I used to work with brushes.
- Really?
- Here you go.
Sorry, but could you move?
I'll start.
(Hippie Kim looks extraordinary.)
Sir, can you move?
- You're in the way.
- I quit. I'm going back.
(The second customer's aesthetic: Hippie makeup)
What did you use to draw your eyebrows?
- Why is it cakey?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- Curl your eyelashes.
- I did it.
- Did you?
- Work on her first. I'll do myself.
I'll do myself.
This...
(Ms. Yum looks risky doing it herself.)
I'll do it. I can do my own makeup.
(Hippie Kim says she'll do it herself.)
- I just need a shadow.
- This.
(Hippie Kim says she'll do it herself.)
I'll smudge it.
(Working on Jung Ah)
(Rubbing)
I didn't do it properly.
(Checking)
- Look at me.
- It's hippie-style, so...
Hold on.
Not with that... That's for the eyebrows.
No, Sun Young, stop.
It's fine. A hippie is...
all about the free-spirited vibe.
My makeup just got ruined.
No, I watched how the Parisienne did it.
- It was...
- Wait, Sun Young. Give me that.
(Brush taken away from her)
- I want to make it look good.
- No.
Curl her eyelashes.
Then close your eyes for a second.
(Closing)
- Like...
- I'll just apply the pearl.
- The natural vibe.
- I got it.
I'll make it look more free-spirited.
This... Why did you colour under your eyes?
- I didn't colour there. It smudged.
- I see.
I need to colour under my eyes dark too.
- Oh.
- That's how it should be.
Do I colour under my eyes?
Not you. I'm a hippie, that's why.
- What should I do?
- Do I colour under my eyes?
- You need to.
- Oh, yes.
(Applying mascara)
(Recolouring under her eyes)
- What is it?
- I don't know. I'm confused.
Here are the eyelashes.
I can put them on.
- You can?
- Yes.
- I'm suddenly... Let me see.
- Is this wrong?
Dear viewers, I'll put on fake eyelashes.
Strip lashes, which were popular in the 90s.
(She communicates with the viewers in between.)
How does it look?
Do I look like a hippie?
- She's so funny.
- It has the hippie vibe.
Sun Young, you're...
(How a Korean hippie is born)
- This is crazy.
- Look at me.
Hippie vibe.
(The other side too)
(Laughing)
How is it?
My eyes look huge.
I can't close my eyes.
- Don't make me laugh.
- I can't close my eyes.
Look. I closed my eyes, but it feels like they're open.
(It's a bit scary at this point.)
This is so scary.
(She looks scary too.)
I look so scary.
I don't think that's it.
(Ms. Yum looks equally frightening.)
Red would look nice.
I have red.
I'll draw freckles.
- What do you draw freckles with?
- Like this.
Hold on.
- Why?
- It's too thick.
How are the freckles?
They're too big.
It's a bit scary.
Is it?
(Producing gigantic freckles)
Sun Young, I'll do it for you. I have it here.
Sun Young, stop.
(The tool is taken away for the 2nd time.)
- It has to be visible in photos.
- I'll do it for you.
(Urgent tapping)
(She fixes the freckles.)
You can relax your eyes.
(Tapping)
The freckles look completely different.
As expected from an art student.
- The freckles...
- Please don't make me laugh.
But I look like I'm drunk.
The drunkenness vibe won't go away.
Is it not? Hold on.
I look like a drunk woman who has a lot of freckles.
Hold on.
I'm almost done.
Look at me.
- You're so good.
- Hold still.
You're really good at drawing freckles.
(Adding a mole to her makeup)
- Gosh, Jung Ah.
- It needs to be thicker.
- Do I look scary?
- Your lips look gorgeous.
Do they? Great.
You're becoming sexy.
I want to fix my hair in advance. I have no mousse.
Let me see.
- You're so good at makeup.
- What can I add?
Done.
(Yoon Seo got herself a full glow up too.)
This is enough.
(Her beauty salon closes with success.)
Let's go on an outing to the salon.
- Let's go.
- Mother, wait for me.
Hurry up.
(Winking)
We're off to a salon.
Get in.
(Let's go to a salon to style the hair nicely.)
- I'll start driving.
- Okay.
(Everyone sets off to get their hair done.)
It's hot.
Shall I turn on the music?
Sure.
(It's disco time, baby)
(Beat on)
(Dancing)
(Everyone, get ready!)
(One, two, three, four.)
(Disco time starts.)
Who's the singer?
It's KOYOTE.
- KOYOTE.
- "Pure Love."
(Back to the end of the century)
(Singing)
(Cheering)
(Dancing)
(Shoulder Dance Sisters)
Turn on the shiny lights.
(As you wish.)
- Wearing the makeup makes me dance.
- Right, it's...
("Eve's Warning" is a must-listen too.)
(Are you already tired?)
(She still can't close her eyes.)
The songs from the 90s are so much more exciting.
- The disco vibe.
- Exactly.
It's so nice.
(They excitedly charge the back-in-the-days vibe.)
(The siblings have entered the downtown of Taean.)
Right, I need to wear the hairpiece.
- I brought it.
- You brought a hairpiece?
I brought a hairpiece.
- The coloured one.
- Blonde.
- Amazing. That's right.
(Sun Young is on a different level.)
Really?
It won't be easy to beat you.
Is this a competition?
Will Sun Young win again?
Am I going to win again?
You rank first in every match.
Starting with the cooking competition.
(They suddenly get competitive when they're taking a family photo.)
We'll arrive in 50m.
The first group, get out here.
Okay.
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo will get out here first.)
We're parting ways here?
Yes.
See you after our hair is done.
- Bye.
- Jung Ah...
(They'll fix their hair and get changed...)
(before going to the studio.)
Let's get going.
Yes, let's go.
(Sun Young and You Seok head to another salon.)
- Hello.
- We came to do our hair.
(The neighbourhood salon has the warm and nostalgic vibe.)
(Welcome to Blonde Hair Salon.)
- Hello.
- The makeup today...
looks like a goblin.
- We're taking a family portrait.
- What's this?
We'll be wearing the clothes from the 70s and 80s.
It'll be nice...
to give volume to hair.
Yes.
- I'll add volume here...
- Yes.
- and over here.
- Okay.
Since you have a small face.
(Let's get styled up.)
(Rolling...)
(and rolling)
(Using plenty of spray)
You look pretty even with that makeup.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Turning into a fashionista)
You look pretty.
You have an amazing side profile.
(Bantering)
Thinking about cooking like this...
(The reality hits her.)
My gosh.
I wonder where Sun Young and You Seok went.
"Freestyle Salon."
That's an awesome name. "Freestyle Salon."
Be free.
(Even the name is free-spirited.)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(The two most free-spirited members enter.)
I'll put my things here.
I want hippie hair.
(Hippie?)
Later...
A hippie vibe.
I brought these blonde hairpieces.
She got hairpieces.
(A hippie's must-have item, hairpieces)
She's serious.
- A hippie...
- There's a reason she won.
I told you.
I didn't know.
After wearing this,
I'll attach them.
This kind of vibe.
- You don't need to do your hair.
- Like this.
- Just wear the hairpieces.
- Just need to add volume here.
You want to add a lot of volume or just enough to look natural?
- A lot.
- A lot, right?
I need to win.
I don't want it to be pretty. I want it to be funny.
I don't think I can rank high.
Here...
Is there more I can add to my makeup?
If I knew this would happen, I'd have chosen a stronger concept.
A red shirt...
and pants which is very tight here...
and flared here.
You need a lot of brushes to do this, don't you?
I have tons of them.
- It has the vibe of that era.
- Yes.
I feel it already. You look so pretty.
You're so pretty.
- You look so pretty.
- You're making my heart flutter.
- This look on you...
- Thank you.
You look so pretty.
(Showering her with praises)
Do you eat preservatives? You don't age at all.
- Exactly.
- My goodness.
(Feeling shy)
Which brand do you take?
I just eat the ones in pastries.
- Those?
- I eat those in pastry and snacks.
I eat anything I can find.
Eating that didn't cross my mind...
because it says not to eat.
(She learned the secret to her young face.)
(Here comes the spray.)
You're using the spray like they did for my Miss Korea hair.
(The styling reminds her of that time.)
It's been a while since someone used that much spray on you, right?
- They all backcombed the hair then.
- This is backcombing.
- I get to do this today.
- Backcombing.
People use the English term nowadays.
(Showing off her backcombing skills)
We thought the world would fall if we didn't backcomb our hair.
- "The world would fall."
- We thought the world would fall.
Even if you roll around, the hair stays.
- It lasts until tomorrow.
Until tomorrow.
(It's fixed so well that it lasts until tomorrow.)
(Spraying)
- You're using the whole bottle.
- No.
(She sprays...)
(and sprays.)
This is how you do it.
(Spraying)
(She's practically coating her hair.)
The smoke...
I'm going to wash my hair tonight.
- This...
- Yes.
(Full of smoke)
(Just like the smoke, her hair gets fuller.)
That's a bit too much.
(She has another crown.)
That's so funny.
- I'm a bit scared now.
- Is this enough?
- I'll leave it to you.
- Okay.
(Yoon Seo's turn has arrived.)
Looking at it here, it's like I barely did any makeup.
I thought it was quite heavy.
I thought I put it on pretty heavily,
but now it looks like I'm bare-faced.
Let me put on something more.
I'm getting competitive. It's too... Hold on.
I'll do this.
- I'm sorry, but the bag...
- Your lipstick is too light.
Put on a brighter colour.
And some blush.
- Blush.
- Yes, add more blush.
Okay, I'll try it.
(She adds blush and lipstick.)
This is no joke.
(And the unending amount of spray)
(The boss is as serious as Yoon Seo.)
(She sprays all over her hair.)
(Intense backcombing)
My gosh.
(Insane hair volume)
(Surprised)
(Who are you?)
The more volume your hair has, the richer you are.
- Then I'll add more.
- No, it's okay.
- No.
- I'll add more.
It's okay.
- Stay still.
- This kind of...
One more time?
Glitter.
Glitter?
(Suddenly adding glitter)
It's not.
What's not?
- Boss, what's not?
- Your hair.
They'll disappear.
What will disappear?
(Revisiting Yoon Seo's aesthetic: Hip hop)
This...
(A salon in the wilderness)
This is my first time.
You can simply wear clothes, and your hair will remain the same.
(What about Sun Young and You Seok?)
My name is Jennica Kim.
How do I look?
My gosh.
(Blonde)
(Flick)
Dear viewers, how do I look?
I'm the aunt of this house.
I lived in the States for one month,
where I found my way of fashion.
My name is Jennica.
(But I feel a bit shy.)
Because I went to the USA,
I mostly forgot my Korean.
I bought this in the USA too.
Let's try it on.
In California, even men wear these.
But there's a downside to it.
They look pretty, but you can't walk in them.
You can only stand.
I'm from the USA.
(What kind of country is the USA?)
I can only walk this far.
(I can only walk this far.)
I'll leave it to you.
(The aunt with a strong character)
Please help me avoid ranking last.
(The gamer is nervous.)
Done.
What's your name again? Erica?
Oh, my gosh.
Are you crazy?
- You're my nephew.
- What?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you remember me? I'm your aunt.
- We're taking a family portrait, - Aunt.
- so even though I'm so busy, - Aunt Erica.
- I came here from the States.
- Aunt Erica.
- Yes?
- Have some bread.
- Bread?
- Bread.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Korean bread.
- I love it!
- Yes.
- Oh, my gosh!
I love it! Bread!
Aunt.
Are you okay?
Why? Do I look like I have issues?
I'm very happy right now.
(No problem.)
I'd like you to style it...
to resemble the hairstyle from that time.
(The gamer can't lose.)
(Blow-dry the hair.)
(Here comes the backcombing.)
- Is it going well?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Very competitive)
Boss, how long have you been doing this job?
Since I was 19.
You started at 19, which means it's been 10 years now.
Hasn't it been ten years?
Which colour was popular back then?
(He gets the hairpieces for making the boss happy.)
- Red?
- Yes.
Red?
Or orange or pink?
The back of my hair is too short, so I want to have it reshaped.
- Should I put on more extensions?
- Yes.
(Getting more stylish)
- What do you think?
- Make it more old-school.
(A tough guy with a super old-school style...)
(is being born.)
(I'm ready to take 1st place.)
I want to define the shape by doing this.
Auntie.
Gosh. Look at him!
(Crumpling)
Hey, you!
- Hold on, Auntie.
- Gosh. You look so fine.
(Taean in 2026)
(Taean in...)
(Taean in 1979)
(To turn back the clock on their youth, )
(a group of 4 men and women are here.)
(This show will shake up the Korean fashion scene.)
(The 60s-90s Retro Fashion Show at Fresh off the Sea)
(We'll take you to the media frenzy, )
(the runway at a photo studio.)
Am I the first to go?
(Welcome to the show.)
Gosh. What do I do?
This is harder than acting. Give me a second.
One, two, three.
(Yoon Seo, the hip-hop girl)
(Striking a pose)
(Yoon Seo turns.)
Are we good?
(Perfectly recreating the youth in the 1990s)
(Loaded with bubbly energy and talents, )
(the hip-hop icon of the past is back!)
(The bold combination of the denim overalls...)
(and a red bandana is the highlight.)
(Twitching)
Gosh.
(It's a bit too much to handle.)
It's too much.
Okay. I'm fine. Yes.
The look I was going for today...
was Lee Hyo Ri of Fin.K.L.
As for the makeup,
I thought Jung Ah and Sun Young would be dominating.
They went so bold,
so I had to put on more makeup at the end.
That's all.
Which way? Okay. Hold on.
(Exiting in a hurry out of embarrassment)
(She checked off a big one.)
(Next to make an entrance is a model in striking red tights.)
(Jung Ah, the epitome of retro fashion)
That's crazy. She is an experienced pro.
That's how it should be done.
Jung Ah.
(Sophisticated and aloof)
(Walking the runway indifferently)
(Striking a pose)
Where should I look?
(Romance meets boldness.)
(The return of the 1970's modern girl)
(A miniskirt and a bob, the signature of the new generation)
(And the red tights)
(She may look a little aloof, )
(but she's an ordinary girl who lives for fun.)
(Drawing all eyes)
Why do you look so natural, Jung Ah?
(Bursting out the twist when there is no music)
This is how it's done.
I'm so new to this. Jung Ah.
(Shocked)
I'm really bad at this.
Isn't it fabulous? Yes.
Yoon Seo helped me with the makeup.
The key is these bold colours.
This combination of colours.
Also, the sequins, the belt, and the headband.
That's it.
(Sassy)
I feel like I'm out of my league.
Tell the next person to hurry.
This is what experience gets you.
- I lost already.
- Let's see who's next.
- I lost. I'll finish last.
- I can hear them coming up.
(Groaning)
Where?
- It's Sun Young.
- Sun Young's loud.
Where?
I came from the US.
(The third model, Aunt Jennica from the US)
I lived in the US for a month, so Korea feels foreign to me.
(Covering her mouth)
These shoes are for standing.
- They're not for walking.
- Look at her heels.
(She's rocking 15cm heels.)
I came from the US. I'm Jennica.
(Stumbling)
It's so hard to stand still.
(A free-spirited lady who crossed the Pacific)
(Soaked in American culture, )
(she decked out in 1970s hippie fashion.)
Yes. This is the smell of Korea.
(After living overseas for a month, )
Korea, I love it.
(she has come back to her homeland she missed...)
(to finally be in the retro fashion show.)
Gosh.
You should've captured it.
You should've shot me falling.
Why did you miss it?
I was so...
(It was captured very well.)
Our viewers.
I'm doing my very best, as you can see.
If it made you laugh while eating,
I'm happy to take the fall.
I'm fine.
(Don't get confused.)
(She's Jennica, not Sun Young.)
(Welcome back to Korea, Jennica.)
(A pose...)
(master)
(Bursting out some dance moves)
I'm not used to speaking Korean...
after living overseas for a month.
It's crazy.
(She feels overwhelmed again.)
Hey, Jung Ah!
(She found the eldest sister in red.)
My niece.
Hey, Jung Ah.
(Pecking)
I heard about the photoshoot.
I was so busy in California,
but I had to come.
- It's insane.
- I got on the airplane ASAP.
Good job.
How do I look, Sister?
I'll be wearing these...
to season the dried radish later on.
(Jennica still thinks like Sun Young.)
Gosh. Yoon Seo, my niece!
Your auntie is here, Yoon Seo.
- Goodness.
- I missed you, Sister.
- I'm not your sister.
- Then...
- I'm your aunt.
- My aunt.
- It's Auntie Jennica.
- She was my aunt.
Jennica is young. Gosh. Seriously.
By the way, don't you feel hot?
I'm so hot.
(Laughing)
But I can tough it out in the heat.
Be patient.
Does patient mean to endure?
- Good.
- What is "patient?"
I don't know.
- Yes.
- Where is You Seok?
You Soon?
- You Soon is coming up right now.
- You Soon.
You Soon shocked me.
He looks so good.
- Gosh.
- He's coming.
(The last model strides in.)
Come on.
- Come on.
(The last model, You Soon, the tough guy)
It's crazy.
(Throwing on)
(Unleashing his wild energy)
Why is everyone so good at this?
- "I'm James Dean."
- Gosh.
- Are you James Dean?
- Why is he crushing it?
(Do you know You James?)
(The grand return...)
(of the 1970s rebellious bad boy)
(Denim-on-denim and a red scarf)
(The epitome of a Western tough guy)
(The man of the American West...)
(is here to conquer the Korean West.)
(Clacking)
Please go on.
(Laughing)
(Anyway, he's You James Dean.)
(He has an irresistible charm.)
(But don't fall for him.)
- Why is he crushing it?
- Are you James Dean?
Gosh. I lost. I need to redo this.
I need to come back.
- I'll make the entrance again.
- Where are you going?
(Turning one more time)
(Putting on a good show)
(Celebrating)
- He's crazy.
- Good job.
- Why is he so good?
- He's awesome.
(He's not done yet.)
- He's my nephew.
- Okay.
You look amazing, You Soon.
He was influenced by his aunt...
- after staying with her.
- He speaks good Korean.
(He was influenced, all right.)
(He was heavily influenced by her.)
(Madness and fear)
Jung Ah, what do we do?
We can't pull that off because we're so pretty.
I'm so shocked and touched.
- Hold my hand.
- What do I do?
I'm no match for them.
Hold on. You Seok.
We're a couple.
(The two went on...)
(to let it all out.)
Okay. Good.
(Admiring them)
- Let's take a family photo.
- How could you, You Seok?
Gosh. I'm back to myself. I was possessed by someone else.
Jung Ah, you look so pretty, though.
- You're really pretty.
- Especially the tights.
(Thanks for the compliments.)
- You're in your element.
- It's...
Shouldn't we go clubbing like this?
- I saw you going crazy.
- Hello. We'll take a family photo.
(It's really time to take a family photo.)
(First, they will take solo shots to commemorate the moment.)
You're crushing it, Jung Ah.
(Yoon Seo is crushing it too.)
It's S.O.S.
- Did you say S.O.S?
- Yes, S.O.S.
(Glaring)
Please take photos of me.
(Aunt Jennica gets solo shots too.)
(Stumbling)
Please give me a second. It was nothing.
(She's still not used to the killer heels.)
(You James Dean is looking cool too.)
(He even takes it to the floor.)
Gosh. My goodness.
(After taking the solo shots, )
It's insane.
(it's time for a family photo.)
(Cracking up)
(The family looks a bit eccentric.)
(But they will remember today's happy and fun moments...)
- Thank you.
(with their first family photo.)
- Good job.
(The siblings come home after shopping for groceries.)
- Let's rest for a bit, Jung Ah.
- Let's get some rest.
Gosh. What a lovely day.
(Jennica lounges in the afternoon sun.)
(The sun above their heads sinks toward the ground.)
(And evening has come, painting the fields in golden hues.)
Can someone help me carry it?
It's too heavy for me.
(You Seok goes to the kitchen to help Jung Ah.)
- The pig's feet?
- Yes.
(Pig's feet!)
- Where should I put them?
- By the faucet.
I need to wash them.
(What is their dinner menu made with this many pig's feet?)
We'll make jokbal.
We'll also make garlic sauce with the garlic we received today.
And we'll make the bibim makguksu, the spicy buckwheat noodles.
And stir-fried garlic scapes with dried shrimp. That's all.
(The four siblings harvested...)
(Seosan's garlic, raised in an open field under the sun.)
(The garlic will add a pungent aroma to the table.)
Hello.
I'm going to make the seasoned dried radish.
Today, I'm the chef of the seasoned dried radish.
(You Seok's seasoned dried radish to enjoy with jokbal)
(The four siblings get to work to make dinner.)
(The Californian Wasp is the first one to get moving.)
Gosh. This garlic is amazing.
(She admires the garlic they harvested.)
This much?
(Checking the amount by grabbing a handful)
- You'll need more.
- More?
- Yes, it's because...
- Okay.
(Wasp Sun Young does not wait. She goes back before hearing why.)
I need to add some garlic when boiling the pig's feet.
(Adding twice as much)
Will twice as much be enough, Jung Ah?
Yes.
(Final approval)
(The Californian Wasp starts prepping the garlic...)
(after getting the approval.)
I need to sit on the floor.
(She adjusts herself to peel the garlic.)
This garlic is very fresh.
- Is it crazy?
- It's great.
(It's great.)
(Looking at the fresh garlic reminds her of...)
Back in California,
I couldn't find garlic...
that was in good quality like this.
(her one-month stay in California.)
It's really hard to run into garlic that's as fine as this.
What sets Korean garlic apart... What was it?
(She asks because she doesn't know.)
(Laughing)
My hands...
will smell like garlic.
Will you rinse the pig's feet, Yoon Seo?
- Okay.
- Can you touch them?
Yes.
Rinse them in case there's any bone dust.
(Jennica is now on the wooden platform...)
(to peel the garlic.)
I'm trying to peel the garlic when I'm from California.
I'm not used to this.
Do they not eat garlic in California?
- They eat it.
- Do they not have it?
I've never peeled the garlic before.
I'll keep peeling the garlic.
I'll stay seated.
(There is quite a lot of peeled garlic now.)
Please give me the garlic.
(Jung Ah gets ready to make the garlic sauce.)
Yes.
That will be enough.
- Is it enough?
- Yes.
(Is she finally finished peeling garlic?)
(This is enough.)
Peel the rest...
(Peel the garlic to use when boiling the pig's feet.)
- to put in the water.
- Okay.
Please wash it to remove the skin completely.
Next time, let's not harvest garlic.
Let's just buy it.
(Let's buy garlic from a store.)
(Jennica asks or politely threatens the production staff.)
(Now, she's making the sauce.)
(Making garlic sauce, Step 1: Rinse the peeled garlic.)
(Making garlic sauce, Step 1: Mince the garlic.)
(Add the garlic to the chopper.)
(Mincing it with both hands)
(Let me see.)
What?
(It didn't get minced.)
It'll take forever to mince it. It won't work.
I'll try it.
(Let me try it.)
I tried it. You chop it by pushing it.
(Mincing it as if it's propelled by a motor)
(Bending over)
(He must be desperate to mince the garlic.)
- It's not moving inside.
- No. It doesn't work.
(It's still whole.)
Should I pound it?
That's right.
I'll pound it. It'll be done in no time.
- I need to crush it, right?
- Yes.
(He starts to pound it in a mortar, their new weapon.)
(The cameraman approaches.)
I...
I've minced garlic many times.
- Really?
- At my grandma's place,
(He got his garlic-mincing skills at his grandma's place.)
I pounded garlic like this or used a garlic press.
Right. My mom used to use it all the time too.
I minced garlic many times to help my grandma.
(The garlic-mincing prodigy is lost in memories.)
Yes. This is how it's done.
(You Seok, lost in his memories, minces garlic for a long time.)
Is it done?
- Do you want it minced more finely?
- No.
(Thanks to You Seok, the garlic-mincing prodigy, )
(the garlic is finely minced.)
(Sugar)
(Vinegar)
(Oligosaccharide)
(Tuna fish sauce)
(Sesame oil)
(Mix the various ingredients well.)
(Cover it and let it sit for a while.)
(The garlic sauce is done.)
(The water is finally boiling.)
(It's time.)
(She carries the pig's feet rinsed by Yoon Seo.)
(Chef Yum looks more nervous than ever.)
No matter what, I'll make jokbal that doesn't smell bad.
(The reason Chef Yum is so determined...)
(The most crucial part of cooking tasty jokbal...)
(is to remove the pork's strong odour.)
(Lots of ingredients are needed just to remove the odour.)
(It's the most challenging dish ever.)
(Will Jung Ah be able to remove the odour...)
(and make tasty jokbal?)
(Pouring soju, which removes the order well)
We need to remove the foul odour.
That's the most crucial part. Removing the odour.
(After pouring a whole bottle of soju, )
(she places each piece of the chunky pig's feet.)
(Placing them carefully as if it's a ritual)
I need to remove the odour today.
I have to remove it.
(Vowing to remove the odour for many times)
(The last piece of the pig's feet is added to the pot.)
Please don't smell bad.
(She'll boil it for about 20 minutes.)
I need to cook the buckwheat noodles.
No, don't cook the noodles yet.
Cook noodles last, or they'll get soggy.
- You can make the sauce now.
- Okay.
I won't peel the garlic anymore.
(Thick soy sauce)
Nine spoonfuls of the thick soy sauce.
(Yoon Seo pours the soy sauce carefully.)
Okay. I'm done with garlic.
(Gushing out)
(She added about 3 spoonfuls by pouring twice.)
- Four, five, - Is that enough?
six,
seven, eight. Gosh.
Is this enough?
(Carefully)
Nine.
(Pouring carefully when it's too late)
Six spoonfuls of the cooking wine.
Six spoonfuls of vinegar.
(6 spoonfuls of sugar)
(Now, it's time to add chilli powder.)
(She starts pouring the chilli powder.)
Two,
three,
(Pouring while measuring it with her mouth)
four, five,
six.
(Gushing out for the 2nd time)
(Losing all hope)
(She doesn't want to believe it.)
- What happened, Yoon Seo?
- It's nothing.
- Are you okay? Put it up there.
- I'm okay.
(She scoops out her mistake in a hurry.)
(Worried)
You can make the sauce again.
It's not a big deal.
It's okay. I just need to taste it.
(The youngest sister is positive.)
(6 spoonfuls of gochujang)
(Lots of toasted sesame seeds)
(How will Yoon Seo's sauce taste?)
Is it good?
I'm still working on it.
It needs to be more watery...
- to mix it with the noodles later.
- Yes.
(The sauce is way too thick to mix properly.)
- Want to add some pear drink?
- Yes.
(Adding pear juice to sweeten it up and thin out the sauce)
- Gosh.
- It should be more watery.
- I know.
- How did it taste?
- It's too salty.
- Too salty?
Then we should add some more.
(Adding more)
(Yoon Seo tastes it again.)
(Nodding)
(Humming in surprise)
Is it delicious? Is it good to go?
I think it's okay.
Am I wrong? Could you taste it for me?
(She goes to get Chef Yum's approval.)
(Chef Yum tastes it too.)
(Nervous)
It tastes good.
- It's good.
- Is it good?
- Oh, yes.
- Yes.
- Success.
- It's a success.
(Yoon Seo's first makguksu sauce is ready.)
I'll make some seasoned dried radish.
Yes, make some seasoned dried radish.
First, I have to wash dried radish five times.
(You Seok starts by prepping the dried radish.)
As you knead and work it with your hands,
the stiff dried radish gradually becomes soft.
(Keep soaking and massaging it until it's soft)
Actually, it's my first time making it...
so I don't really know.
(The rookie dried radish cook)
You Seok, you can do it.
You can do anything.
(Auntie Jennica's love for her nephew knows no bounds.)
(Fuelled by Auntie Jennica's encouragement)
(He rinses it...)
(again and again.)
(After rinsing it again, )
(he squeezes out the excess water once the dried radish is soaked.)
Cooking wine?
I just do it based on my feeling. Turning it once, twice...
Three times.
Cooking is all about that personal touch.
(After giving it roughly three turns)
I soaked it in cooking wine.
(Letting it marinate for a while)
(Meanwhile, the first round of boiling pig's feet is done.)
(It's time to take it out.)
(Once you pull it out through the steam)
(The pig's feet is deliciously cooked.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(She plans to boil it again after adding spices.)
I'll throw it away over there.
(Jung Ah is about to wash the pot before boiling again.)
Isn't it heavy?
(Lifting easily)
- Move out of the way.
- Over here...
- What's the matter?
- What is it?
(You Seok goes running at the sound of an urgent call.)
My goodness.
There's a snake!
(There's a snake.)
(A snake?)
- My gosh.
- Where is it?
- Gosh, there's a snake.
- Where?
Don't go in there!
There's a snake. What are you doing?
- There's a snake.
- Where's the snake?
Where is it?
(Where's the snake?)
Why are you going in there?
Where is it?
- Hey.
- There's a snake.
It's dangerous. Don't go there.
- Hey.
- There's a snake.
(What do we do?)
- Hey.
- You Seok.
Get out of there, You Seok.
What is he doing?
(Worried about You Seok, Yoon Seo also goes inside.)
Oh, no. You Seok.
You Seok, come back here.
You can't use that. No way.
- What's wrong with you?
- Gosh.
What happened?
(A mission given to Chef Yum for tonight's dinner)
(Make jokbal!)
(The siblings' best dish is born.)
(Featuring all handmade garlic sauce)
(A taste so incredible you'll question your own tongue)
(Chewy like jelly)
(An especially bittersweet night in Taean)
(Every day was eventful.)
(The events aren't over yet.)
(Did the production crew do it again?)
(What's wrong with them?)
(Did the siblings get owned?)
(Yoon Seo, the optimistic girl)
(She shows her dark side.)
(Your opponent is chickens.)
(Gasping)
(Horrified)
(A showdown with chickens in its raw form)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young begins a battle of her own.)
Isn't it too thick?
(Anxiety)
(Lack of confidence)
(I still want to please Jung Ah.)
(A morning without Captain Yum equals...)
(a disaster.)
(How will the loudest morning at the siblings' end?)